welink.com 2005-04-10

# Advertise with Us I Contact Us I About Us I Privacy Policy I Term

### Privacy Policy 

WelinkTravel provides easy to use services. The Services may also be located on third party web sites and/or applications. The Services are made available by WelinkTravel.com and its subsidiaries and affiliates. WelinkTravel values its users and their concerns about privacy. WelinkTravel takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

### What this Privacy Policy Covers

This Privacy Policy covers WelinkTravel’s treatment of personally identifiable information that WelinkTravel collects when you are on the WelinkTravel site, and when you use WelinkTravel’s services. This policy also covers WelinkTravel’s treatment of any personally identifiable information that WelinkTravel’s business partners share with WelinkTravel or that WelinkTravel may collect on a partner's site. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that WelinkTravel does not own, control or to people that WelinkTravel does not employ or manage. 

### Third Party Banner Ads.

We use other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

WelinkTravel will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. 

WelinkTravel will only send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 

We have your consent to share the information; 

We need to share your information in order to provide the product or service you have requested; 

We need to send the information to companies that work on behalf of WelinkTravel to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.); 

We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or 

We find that your actions on our web sites violate the WelinkTravel Terms of Service or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

WelinkTravel may edit this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages. 

### Questions or Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions complete a feedback form or send an email to [info@welinktravel.com](mailto:info@welinktravel.com)
